So last week, two FBI agents showed up at my door and had some questions about things that I've
posted on social media. They were investigating domestic terrorism, I believe. Shout out to my
agents. I am so honored that you watch my content. Next time, please give me a heads up or something
so I can make you some tea or coffee. And I hope you're watching this video because I do have an
important question for you at the end. My two federal agents were very concerned with this
video that I made calling on organizers to organize better. They were highly concerned that I had
shared addresses of weapon manufacturers in this country and they wanted to know why I had done
that and what were my intentions with sharing that video and essentially tried to accuse me of
inciting violence. And I just want to make it abundantly clear publicly that I did not and do
not call for violence against individuals or property that you care so much about. With that said, this is
a perfect opportunity to remind everyone, especially you federal agents, of the Leahy Law. What is the
Leahy Law, you may ask? Well, let's read it directly from the U.S. Department of State's website.
The term Leahy Law refers to two statutory provisions prohibiting the U.S. government from using funds for
assistance to units of foreign security forces where there is credible information implicating that
unit in the commission of gross violation of human rights. Let's translate that into plain English.
The U.S. government is forbidden from selling weapons to or funding a foreign entity that is
violating human rights. Our government is breaking its own law just to support this foreign entity in
the Middle East that has been violating international law for decades and has now committed probably every
single war crime in the book. And this is not me saying it. This is Amnesty International. This is the
UN Council for Human Rights. This is the International Association of Genocide Scholars. Even this country's
own human rights organizations came out and said that this is a genocide. Which brings me back to
this video. Now, I understand that I left things open for interpretation and I didn't provide specific
examples. And yes, people may have taken it as a call for violence. But there are so many things that
citizens can do that do not break the law. For example, protesting on a Monday or any weekday,
any other day but Saturday or Sunday. People can block roads or organize sit-ins at these specific
locations to prevent the flow of weapons being sent to the Middle East. None of these things require
violence. Now, my question to you federal agents, and I really hope you're watching again so that you
can answer this question. Like seriously, if you could DM me, text me, or even just show up at my door
again, just so we can be on the same page on this, it will be super helpful. My question to you is this.
If citizens chose to enforce this law, take it upon themselves to enforce the Leahy Law, because the
government clearly isn't doing it, would that count as domestic terrorism or patriotism? I'll let you chew on that.